yogajournal.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Yoga Journal

This site complies with the following Privacy Policy. By using this site, you indicate your acceptance of _Yoga Journal_ ‘s Online Privacy Policy.

This site collects no personally identifying information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. We do record information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address when you interact with the site. _Yoga Journal_ uses this information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. We also use this information to verify the number of discrete times you visit this web site each day.

The Information We Collect At some Active Interest Media sites, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

There are cases where Active Interest Media may ask you for personally-identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, and email address. Examples include, but are not limited to, online shopping transactions, signing up for an email newsletter, registering on our Sites, or participating in sweepstakes. Active Interest Media will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. Active Interest Media may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; use that information to contact you for informational and promotional purposes; use and disclose that information to third parties to the extent necessary to provide you with products or services you have ordered.

In addition, we may place a “cookie” in the browser files of a user’s computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information although it will enable us to relate a user’s use of our sites to information that the user has specifically and knowingly provided to us.

A user’s personally identifying information may be used for marketing and promotional purposes and we may share the information with others if the user has not advised us of his or her preference not to be included in such an exchange. Individuals always have the ability to stop their information being used for such purposes.

_Yoga Journal_ may send e-mail to people with whom we have a business relationship.

To ensure the security of your data, including address information and credit card numbers, _Yoga Journal_ always uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures that protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you.

While we will seek to require third parties with whom we have agreements to follow appropriate privacy policies, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. Our web site contains links, including e-commerce opportunities with affiliates, partners and associates, to other sites that are not maintained by us. If you visit these sites, please look for their privacy policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: (<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>).

We use Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).  
Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).  
We will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick cookie unless you have provided prior affirmative (i.e., opt-in) consent to, that merger.

Children should ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to us or anyone else over the Internet.

Posting comments on YogaJournal.com is subject to additional policies.

Our properties may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software which will allow you to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices with regard to it, please see the [Nielsen Digital Measurement Privacy](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy).
